

### Software Engineer

I've been a software engineer for 3 years working with development of systems web for different clients and during my experience I used many methodologies to manage a process like SCRUM, KABAN and XP. I work with AngularJS and ReactJS but I'm not limited only to this I can work with different frameworks to give the best possible solution for my clients. I wanna reach positions with more responsibility to share knowledge and achieve goals of the company.

# **EDUCATION**

### Universidade UniEvangélica (2018 - 2021)

Bachelor of Software Engineer

## **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

### Squadra Tecnologia (2020 - Present day)

#### **Fullstack Developer**

Client: GrupoLPJ

**Activities and responsibilities:** Create features of the system to manage all flow for emission invoices and control of finances.

Technology Stack: AngularJS, PHP, Laravel, Lumen, GIT, Node.js, YARN, AWS and MySQL.

Client: Pottencial Seguradora

**Activities and responsibilities:** Create system to manage flow of broker to do quotation, policies, emission of contract and to make the life of clients that want a security to something easier.

**Technology Stack:** JavaScript, React Js, Redux, ContextAPI, Webpack, SASS, Single SPA, Azure Devops and GIT.

# Inline Engenharia (2019 - 2020)

#### Front-End Developer

**Activities and responsibilities:** Create pages web to own company and maintainability of systems legacies. Create applications for desktop and mobile.

**Technology Stack:** JavaScript, ReactJS, React Native, NodeJS, PHP, Codeigniter, Electron.

# Fábrica de Tecnologias Turing (2018)

#### Requirements Analyst

**Activities and responsibilities:** Create documents of requirements, user story, case of use and prototyping. **Technology Stack:** Bizage Modeler, Scrum and Pencil Project .

## **SKILLS**

**Operating systems:** MS-Windows, Linux.

**Languages:** PHP, Javascript, Typescript.

Internet / Web: Node.JS, ReactJS, NextJS, Express, Laravel, Lumen.

**Programming/Tools:** Visual Studio Code, PHPStorm.

**Libraries:** Express, JWT, Bootstrap, Material-UI, ChartJS, TypeORM, Sequelize, XDebug

**Databases:** MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB.

Cloud: AWS, Heroku, GitLab

# LANGUAGES

Portuguese (Native)

English (Intermediate)